update sets set questions='[{"question":"வணக்கம்","answers":[{"label":"சரி","correct":false,"id":0,"answerAudio":"0f0b9085-ab04-4f79-858c-902426e1186d"},{"label":"நன்றி","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"89fae132-ecbb-4d1c-8be8-a62e444696c6"},{"label":"வணக்கம்","correct":true,"id":2,"answerAudio":"71c705c3-ef37-4de2-bc69-c89f01618bdc"},{"label":"பிறகு சந்திப்போம்","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"4f1602e7-4f81-4b28-a933-538f7fc00e53"}],"id":0,"prompt":"How do you say Hello in Tamil?","questionAudio":"71c705c3-ef37-4de2-bc69-c89f01618bdc","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"காலை வணக்கம்","answers":[{"label":"காலை வணக்கம்","correct":true,"id":0,"answerAudio":"b63aade3-b4c9-49ae-819e-6484cf1ce9ec"},{"label":"மாலை வணக்கம்","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"3ec27acc-e415-450b-9c5c-fe13f61a44c1"},{"label":"பிறகு சந்திப்போம்","correct":false,"id":2,"answerAudio":"4f1602e7-4f81-4b28-a933-538f7fc00e53"},{"label":"வரவேற்பு","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"dd9b50ba-85a3-43ee-91d0-1b08e3170868"}],"id":1,"prompt":"How do you say Good morning in Tamil?","questionAudio":"b63aade3-b4c9-49ae-819e-6484cf1ce9ec","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"மதிய வணக்கம்","answers":[{"label":"காலை வணக்கம்","correct":false,"id":0,"answerAudio":"b63aade3-b4c9-49ae-819e-6484cf1ce9ec"},{"label":"மாலை வணக்கம்","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"3ec27acc-e415-450b-9c5c-fe13f61a44c1"},{"label":"மதிய வணக்கம்","correct":true,"id":2,"answerAudio":"18a87e50-2eb9-4026-a050-1717318dda08"},{"label":"பிறகு சந்திப்போம்","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"4f1602e7-4f81-4b28-a933-538f7fc00e53"}],"id":2,"prompt":"How do you say Good afternoon in Tamil?","questionAudio":"18a87e50-2eb9-4026-a050-1717318dda08","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"மாலை வணக்கம்","answers":[{"label":"மாலை வணக்கம்","correct":true,"id":0,"answerAudio":"0f03fb0c-3693-4df6-89f4-7ff9393571b3"},{"label":"இல்லை","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"e8e5814b-073f-4765-8b2e-2d6eab5afa90"},{"label":"பிரியாவிடை","correct":false,"id":2,"answerAudio":"65292435-1f3d-48d4-9e84-bcf3b65e1196"},{"label":"ஆம்","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"5dba7e4b-519b-4a1b-95ab-d1a12f2369bc"}],"id":3,"prompt":"How do you say Good evening in Tamil","questionAudio":"3ec27acc-e415-450b-9c5c-fe13f61a44c1","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"பிரியாவிடை","answers":[{"label":"வாழ்த்துக்கள்","correct":false,"id":0,"answerAudio":"ce509396-2260-429a-9478-3f0139a12aff"},{"label":"இரவு வணக்கம்","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"0f03fb0c-3693-4df6-89f4-7ff9393571b3"},{"label":"இல்லை","correct":false,"id":2,"answerAudio":"e8e5814b-073f-4765-8b2e-2d6eab5afa90"},{"label":"பிரியாவிடை","correct":true,"id":3,"answerAudio":"65292435-1f3d-48d4-9e84-bcf3b65e1196"}],"id":4,"prompt":"How do you say Goodbye in Tamil?","questionAudio":"65292435-1f3d-48d4-9e84-bcf3b65e1196","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"வரவேற்பு","answers":[{"label":"இல்லை","correct":false,"id":0,"answerAudio":"e8e5814b-073f-4765-8b2e-2d6eab5afa90"},{"label":"வரவேற்பு","correct":true,"id":1,"answerAudio":"dd9b50ba-85a3-43ee-91d0-1b08e3170868"},{"label":"வாழ்த்துக்கள்","correct":false,"id":2,"answerAudio":"ce509396-2260-429a-9478-3f0139a12aff"},{"label":"மிக்க நன்றி","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"a21f6a01-d1b6-4686-9024-07a5f4c59b0c"}],"id":5,"prompt":"How do you say Welcome in Tamil?","questionAudio":"dd9b50ba-85a3-43ee-91d0-1b08e3170868","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"நன்றி","answers":[{"label":"சரி","correct":false,"id":0,"answerAudio":"0f0b9085-ab04-4f79-858c-902426e1186d"},{"label":"ஆம்","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"5dba7e4b-519b-4a1b-95ab-d1a12f2369bc"},{"label":"நன்றி","correct":true,"id":2,"answerAudio":"89fae132-ecbb-4d1c-8be8-a62e444696c6"},{"label":"இல்லை","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"e8e5814b-073f-4765-8b2e-2d6eab5afa90"}],"id":6,"prompt":"How do you say Thank You in Tamil?","questionAudio":"89fae132-ecbb-4d1c-8be8-a62e444696c6","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"சரி","answers":[{"label":"சரி","correct":true,"id":0,"answerAudio":"0f0b9085-ab04-4f79-858c-902426e1186d"},{"label":"வணக்கம்","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"71c705c3-ef37-4de2-bc69-c89f01618bdc"},{"label":"பிரியாவிடை","correct":false,"id":2,"answerAudio":"65292435-1f3d-48d4-9e84-bcf3b65e1196"},{"label":"வரவேற்பு","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"dd9b50ba-85a3-43ee-91d0-1b08e3170868"}],"id":7,"prompt":"How do you say OK in Tamil?","questionAudio":"0f0b9085-ab04-4f79-858c-902426e1186d","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"ஆம்","answers":[{"label":"இல்லை","correct":false,"id":0,"answerAudio":"e8e5814b-073f-4765-8b2e-2d6eab5afa90"},{"label":"ஆம்","correct":true,"id":1,"answerAudio":"5dba7e4b-519b-4a1b-95ab-d1a12f2369bc"},{"label":"மிக்க நன்றி","correct":false,"id":2,"answerAudio":"a21f6a01-d1b6-4686-9024-07a5f4c59b0c"},{"label":"பிரியாவிடை","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"65292435-1f3d-48d4-9e84-bcf3b65e1196"}],"id":8,"prompt":"How do you say Yes in Tamil?","questionAudio":"5dba7e4b-519b-4a1b-95ab-d1a12f2369bc","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"இல்லை","answers":[{"label":"இல்லை","correct":true,"id":0,"answerAudio":"e8e5814b-073f-4765-8b2e-2d6eab5afa90"},{"label":"பிரியாவிடை","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"65292435-1f3d-48d4-9e84-bcf3b65e1196"},{"label":"வாழ்த்துக்கள்","correct":false,"id":2,"answerAudio":"ce509396-2260-429a-9478-3f0139a12aff"},{"label":"சரி","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"0f0b9085-ab04-4f79-858c-902426e1186d"}],"id":9,"prompt":"How do you say No in Tamil?","questionAudio":"e8e5814b-073f-4765-8b2e-2d6eab5afa90","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"வாழ்த்துக்கள்","answers":[{"label":"பிரியாவிடை","correct":false,"id":0,"answerAudio":"65292435-1f3d-48d4-9e84-bcf3b65e1196"},{"label":"மிக்க நன்றி","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"a21f6a01-d1b6-4686-9024-07a5f4c59b0c"},{"label":"இரவு வணக்கம்","correct":false,"id":2,"answerAudio":"0f03fb0c-3693-4df6-89f4-7ff9393571b3"},{"label":"வாழ்த்துக்கள்","correct":true,"id":3,"answerAudio":"ce509396-2260-429a-9478-3f0139a12aff"}],"id":10,"prompt":"How do you say Congratulations in Tamil?","questionAudio":"ce509396-2260-429a-9478-3f0139a12aff","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":false},{"question":"மிக்க நன்றி","answers":[{"label":"வரவேற்பு","correct":false,"id":0,"answerAudio":"dd9b50ba-85a3-43ee-91d0-1b08e3170868"},{"label":"பிரியாவிடை","correct":false,"id":1,"answerAudio":"65292435-1f3d-48d4-9e84-bcf3b65e1196"},{"label":"மிக்க நன்றி","correct":true,"id":2,"answerAudio":"a21f6a01-d1b6-4686-9024-07a5f4c59b0c"},{"label":"வாழ்த்துக்கள்","correct":false,"id":3,"answerAudio":"ce509396-2260-429a-9478-3f0139a12aff"}],"id":11,"prompt":"How do you say \"Thank you very much\" in Tamil?","questionAudio":"a21f6a01-d1b6-4686-9024-07a5f4c59b0c","answerAudio":true,"showQuestion":false,"last":true}]' where id='x-CDhM9k'

Also, fix onru in tamil numbers